Uh, you know, the other sector that's in
focus is the non life insurance sector
and
it delivered a solid FY26 overall with
premiums growing nearly 10% 3.25 lakh
crore in terms of collections. Growth
has
has led in fact by standalone health
insurers which is SAHI SAHIs as they
call it. Anurag here with all of the
highlights with regard to the non life
insurance data which has come through
for the month of March.
Non life insurance industry has shown a
growth of 10% in FY26 and premium has
reached to the mark of 3.25 lakh crore
from 2.96 lakh crore.
For a standalone health insurance
companies, there is a growth of 20% with
a premium of 38,000 crore. If you talk
about
listed companies then
PSU PSU insurance company New India has
shown a growth of 11% with a premium of
42,800 crore. ICICI Lombard has shown a
growth of 7% in FY26 with
premium of 28,700 crore. Star Health
Insurance standalone health insurance
company has shown a growth of 11.3% with
a premium of 18,600 crore. Niva Bupa is
the fastest
growing company
in FY26
in a listed space with a 27%
growth. So, last year
premium was 6,762
crore which has increased to 8,500.
In the month of March also, there is a
growth of companies has shown a growth
of 22%.
If you talk about the listed companies,
the New India 13%
growth, ICICI Lombard 21% growth,
GoDigit 10%, Star Health has shown a
growth of 16% and Niva Bupa has shown a
growth of 38%
in month of March.